how about this insurance space that has
suddenly seen a lot of traction over the
last 10 days odd stocks like s SP life
htfc live they're always in among the
top movers within the Nifty or maybe
even in the Eos space LC is coming back
to newah highs how are you looking at
this entire basket see at Goldilocks we
make custom indices you know sometimes
what NC does not give us we make our own
index and that gives us a sense as to
what certain pockets of the market are
doing so last month when we release our
sector Trends report we put out a custom
made Insurance index of about 10 12
stocks and we realized that the 2 to and
a half year underperformance of this
sector has come to an end I mean look at
an sdfc live it's finally trading at
levels of 700 and above and we've been
discussing sdfc live for three years now
so I think insurance as a pack is back I
think there is more upside I think icsi
Lombard has been our top pick in the G
Insurance space and icsi pro and sgfc
live would now be the top pick going
forward and mfsl is probably the STA
performer of the sector and should do
very well over the next 2 to three years
so I think we like this entire space and
there is clearly a lot more catchup
which is now going to play because they
need to cover up for two years of under
performance
[Music]